<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<form xmlns="http://stepsolns.com/eform/v1" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	xsi:schemaLocation="http://stepsolns.com/eform/v1 https://demo.stepsolutions.com/schema/eforms.v1.xsd">
	<page title="Authorization to Obtain Information">
		<section>
			<group labelWidth="400px" title="PART 2"
				style="overflow:auto; height:120px; border:1px solid black">
				<paragragh
					text="I authorize any insurance company, employer, physician, medical professional, hospital, medical facility, pharmacy, pharmacy benefit manager, consumer reporting agency, MIB, Inc. (MIB), or any other person or organization that has any record of information about me to give to Gerber Life Insurance Company, its reinsurers or its authorized representatives, (together, the Company) information about other insurance coverage, employment, age, general character, finances, participation in hazardous activities, medical care or advice about any physical or mental condition, including drug and alcohol treatment information, prescription history records, or other information the Company requires to determine insurability, eligibility for benefits, investigate claims, or support the business operations of the Company related thereto. I authorize Gerber Life Insurance Company or its reinsurers to make a brief report of my personal health information to MIB. I further authorize the sources listed above except MIB to give such information to a consumer reporting agency acting on behalf of Gerber Life Insurance Company. Gerber Life Insurance Company may release information obtained by this Authorization to its reinsurers, to MIB, to other insurers with whom I have policies or to whom I may apply or submit a claim, to other persons or organizations performing business or legal services in connection with an insurance transaction for me, or as may otherwise be lawfully required."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="Any person who knowingly presents a false statement in an application for insurance may be guilty of a criminal offense and subject to penalties under state law. I have received a copy of the Notice of Insurance Information Practices. My authorized representative or I may obtain a copy of this Authorization on request. This Authorization will be valid for 24 months from the date signed. It is the Company's practice to prohibit third parties who lawfully receive nonpublic health or other privacy related information from the Company from re-disclosing or reusing the disclosed information. A photographic copy shall be as valid as the original. I understand that a copy of this authorization will be provided, upon request, to me or a person authorized on my behalf. I understand that disclosure of information to the Company may subject the information to re-disclosure in accordance with the Company's privacy policy and MIB rules. Any such re-disclosed information may no longer be protected by federal rules governing privacy and confidentiality. This authorization may be revoked; however, it may not be revoked during the contestability period of the policy or to the extent the Company has taken action in reliance on this authorization. Notice of revocation may be sent, in writing, to Gerber Life Insurance Company at the address above."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="I have received a copy of the Notice of Insurance Information Practices. I or my authorized representative may obtain a copy of this Authorization on request. This Authorization will be valid for 24 months from the date signed. It is the Company's practice to prohibit third parties who lawfully receive nonpublic health information from re-disclosing or reusing the disclosed information. A photographic copy shall be as valid as the original. I understand that a copy of this authorization will be provided, upon request, to me or a person authorized on my behalf. I understand that disclosure of information to the Company may subject the information to re-disclosure in accordance with the Company's privacy policy and MIB, Inc. rules. This authorization may be revoked; however, it may not be revoked during the contestability period of the policy or to the extent the Company has taken action in reliance on this authorization. Notice of revocation may be sent, in writing, to Gerber Life Insurance Company at the address above."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<displayWhen>#{CASE.contractLocale!="AZ" and CASE.contractLocale!="CA" and CASE.contractLocale!="CT" and CASE.contractLocale!="DC" and CASE.contractLocale!="DE" and CASE.contractLocale!="FL" and CASE.contractLocale!="SD" and CASE.contractLocale!="ND" and CASE.contractLocale!="NY" and CASE.contractLocale!="MT"}</displayWhen>
			</group>
			<group labelWidth="400px"
				style="overflow:auto; height:120px; border:1px solid black">
				<paragragh
					text="I authorize any insurance company, employer, physician, medical professional, hospital, medical facility, pharmacy, consumer reporting agency, or MIB, Inc., that has any record of information about me to give to Gerber Life Insurance Company, its reinsurers or its authorized representatives, (together, the Company) information about other insurance coverage, employment, age, general character, finances, participation in hazardous activities, medical care or advice about any physical or mental condition, including drug and alcohol treatment information, or other information the Company requires to determine insurability, eligibility for benefits, investigate claims, or support the business operations of the Company related thereto. I authorize Gerber Life Insurance Company or its reinsurer to make a brief report of my personal health information to MIB, Inc. (MIB). I further authorize the sources listed above except MIB, Inc. to give such information to a consumer reporting agency acting on behalf of Gerber Life Insurance Company. Gerber Life Insurance Company may release information obtained by this Authorization to its reinsurers or other insurers with whom I have policies or to whom I may apply or submit a claim, to other persons or organizations performing business or legal services in connection with an insurance transaction for me, or as may otherwise be lawfully required."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="I have received a copy of the Notice of Insurance Information Practices. I or my authorized representative may obtain a copy of this Authorization on request. This Authorization will be valid for 24 months from the date signed (180 days in the case of HIV related information). It is the Company's practice to prohibit third parties who lawfully receive nonpublic health information from re-disclosing or reusing the disclosed information. A photographic copy shall be as valid as the original. I understand that a copy of this authorization will be provided, upon request, to me or a person authorized on my behalf. I understand that disclosure of information to the Company may subject the information to re-disclosure in accordance with the Company's privacy policy and MIB, Inc. rules. This authorization may be revoked; however, it may not be revoked during the contestability period of the policy or to the extent the Company has taken action in reliance on this authorization. Notice of revocation may be sent, in writing, to Gerber Life Insurance Company at the address above."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<displayWhen>#{CASE.contractLocale=="AZ"}</displayWhen>
			</group>
			<group labelWidth="400px"
				style="overflow:auto; height:120px; border:1px solid black">
				<paragragh
					text="I authorize any insurance company, employer, physician, medical professional, hospital, medical facility, pharmacy, pharmacy benefit manager, consumer reporting agency, MIB, Inc. (MIB), or any other person or organization that has any record of information about me to give to Gerber Life Insurance Company, its reinsurers or its authorized representatives, (together, the Company) information about other insurance coverage, employment, age, general character, finances, participation in hazardous activities, medical care or advice about any physical or mental condition, including drug and alcohol treatment information, prescription history records, or other information the Company requires to determine insurability, eligibility for benefits, investigate claims, or support the business operations of the Company related thereto. I authorize Gerber Life Insurance Company or its reinsurers to make a brief report of my personal health information to MIB. I further authorize the sources listed above except MIB to give such information to a consumer reporting agency acting on behalf of Gerber Life Insurance Company. Gerber Life Insurance Company may release information obtained by this Authorization to its reinsurers, to MIB, to other insurers with whom I have policies or to whom I may apply or submit a claim, to other persons or organizations performing business or legal services in connection with an insurance transaction for me, or as may otherwise be lawfully required."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="I have received a copy of the Notice of Insurance Information Practices. My authorized representative or I may obtain a copy of this Authorization on request. This Authorization will be valid for 24 months from the date signed. It is the Company's practice to prohibit third parties who lawfully receive nonpublic health or other privacy related information from the Company from re-disclosing or reusing the disclosed information. A photographic copy shall be as valid as the original. I understand that a copy of this authorization will be provided, upon request, to me or a person authorized on my behalf. I understand that disclosure of information to the Company may subject the information to re-disclosure in accordance with the Company's privacy policy and MIB rules. Any such re-disclosed information may no longer be protected by federal rules governing privacy and confidentiality. This authorization may be revoked; however, it may not be revoked during the contestability period of the policy or to the extent the Company has taken action in reliance on this authorization. Notice of revocation may be sent, in writing, to Gerber Life Insurance Company at the address above."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<displayWhen>#{CASE.contractLocale=="SD" or CASE.contractLocale=="DE" or CASE.contractLocale=="ND"}</displayWhen>
			</group>
			<group labelWidth="400px"
				style="overflow:auto; height:120px; border:1px solid black">
				<paragragh
					text="I authorize any insurance company, employer, physician, medical professional, hospital, medical facility, pharmacy, pharmacy benefit manager, consumer reporting agency, or MIB, Inc. (MIB) that has any record of information about me to give to Gerber Life Insurance Company, its reinsurers or its authorized representatives, (together, the Company) information about other insurance coverage, employment, age, general character, finances, participation in hazardous activities, medical care or advice about any physical or mental condition, including drug and alcohol treatment information, prescription history records, or other information the Company requires to determine insurability, eligibility for benefits, investigate claims, or support the business operations of the Company related thereto. I authorize Gerber Life Insurance Company or its reinsurers to make a brief report of my personal health information to MIB. I further authorize the sources listed above except MIB to give such information to a consumer reporting agency acting on behalf of Gerber Life Insurance Company. Gerber Life Insurance Company may release information obtained by this Authorization to its reinsurers, to MIB, to other insurers with whom I have policies or to whom I may apply or submit a claim, to other persons or organizations performing business or legal services in connection with an insurance transaction for me, or as may otherwise be lawfully required."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="I have received a copy of the Notice of Insurance Information Practices. My authorized representative or I may obtain a copy of this Authorization on request. This Authorization will be valid for 24 months from the date signed. It is the Company's practice to prohibit third parties who lawfully receive nonpublic health or other privacy related information from the Company from re-disclosing or reusing the disclosed information. A photographic copy shall be as valid as the original. I understand that a copy of this authorization will be provided, upon request, to me or a person authorized on my behalf. I understand that disclosure of information to the Company may subject the information to re-disclosure in accordance with the Company's privacy policy and MIB rules. Any such re-disclosed information may no longer be protected by federal rules governing privacy and confidentiality. This authorization may be revoked; however, it may not be revoked during the contestability period of the policy or to the extent the Company has taken action in reliance on this authorization. Notice of revocation may be sent, in writing, to Gerber Life Insurance Company at the address above."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<displayWhen>#{CASE.contractLocale=="CA"}</displayWhen>
			</group>
			<group labelWidth="400px"
				style="overflow:auto; height:120px; border:1px solid black">
				<paragragh
					text="I authorize any insurance company, employer, physician, medical professional, hospital, medical facility, pharmacy, pharmacy benefit manager, consumer reporting agency, MIB, Inc. (MIB), or any other person or organization that has any record of information about me to give to Gerber Life Insurance Company, its reinsurers or its authorized representatives, (together, the Company) information about other insurance coverage, employment, age, general character, finances, participation in hazardous activities, medical care or advice about any physical or mental condition, including drug and alcohol treatment information, prescription history records, or other information the Company requires to determine insurability, eligibility for benefits, investigate claims, or support the business operations of the Company related thereto. I authorize Gerber Life Insurance Company or its reinsurers to make a brief report of my personal health information to MIB. I further authorize the sources listed above except MIB to give such information to a consumer reporting agency acting on behalf of Gerber Life Insurance Company. Gerber Life Insurance Company may release information obtained by this Authorization to its reinsurers, to MIB, to other insurers with whom I have policies or to whom I may apply or submit a claim, to other persons or organizations performing business or legal services in connection with an insurance transaction for me, or as may otherwise be lawfully required."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="I have received a copy of the Notice of Insurance Information Practices. My authorized representative or I may obtain a copy of this Authorization on request. This Authorization will be valid for 24 months from the date signed. It is the Company's practice to prohibit third parties who lawfully receive nonpublic health or other privacy related information from the Company from re-disclosing or reusing the disclosed information. A photographic copy shall be as valid as the original. I understand that a copy of this authorization will be provided, upon request, to me or a person authorized on my behalf. I understand that disclosure of information to the Company may subject the information to re-disclosure in accordance with the Company's privacy policy and MIB rules. Any such re-disclosed information may no longer be protected by federal rules governing privacy and confidentiality. This authorization may be revoked; however, it may not be revoked during the contestability period of the policy or to the extent the Company has taken action in reliance on this authorization. Notice of revocation may be sent, in writing, to Gerber Life Insurance Company at the address above."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<displayWhen>#{CASE.contractLocale=="CT"}</displayWhen>
			</group>
			<group labelWidth="400px"
				style="overflow:auto; height:120px; border:1px solid black">
				<paragragh
					text="I authorize any insurance company, employer, physician, medical professional, hospital, medical facility, pharmacy, pharmacy benefit manager, consumer reporting agency, MIB, Inc. (MIB), or any other person or organization that has any record of information about me to give to Gerber Life Insurance Company, its reinsurers or its authorized representatives, (together, the Company) information about other insurance coverage, employment, age, general character, finances, participation in hazardous activities, medical care or advice about any physical or mental condition, including drug and alcohol treatment information, prescription history records, or other information the Company requires to determine insurability, eligibility for benefits, investigate claims, or support the business operations of the Company related thereto. I authorize Gerber Life Insurance Company or its reinsurers to make a brief report of my personal health information to MIB. I further authorize the sources listed above except MIB to give such information to a consumer reporting agency acting on behalf of Gerber Life Insurance Company. Gerber Life Insurance Company may release information obtained by this Authorization to its reinsurers, to MIB, to other insurers with whom I have policies or to whom I may apply or submit a claim, to other persons or organizations performing business or legal services in connection with an insurance transaction for me, or as may otherwise be lawfully required."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="WARNING: It is a crime to provide false or misleading information to an insurer for the purpose of defrauding the insurer or any other person. Penalities include imprisonment and/or fines. In addition, an insurer may deny insurance benefits, if false information materially related to a claim was provided by the applicant."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="I have received a copy of the Notice of Insurance Information Practices. My authorized representative or I may obtain a copy of this Authorization on request. This Authorization will be valid for 24 months from the date signed. It is the Company's practice to prohibit third parties who lawfully receive nonpublic health or other privacy related information from the Company from re-disclosing or reusing the disclosed information. A photographic copy shall be as valid as the original. I understand that a copy of this authorization will be provided, upon request, to me or a person authorized on my behalf. I understand that disclosure of information to the Company may subject the information to re-disclosure in accordance with the Company's privacy policy and MIB rules. Any such re-disclosed information may no longer be protected by federal rules governing privacy and confidentiality. This authorization may be revoked; however, it may not be revoked during the contestability period of the policy or to the extent the Company has taken action in reliance on this authorization. Notice of revocation may be sent, in writing, to Gerber Life Insurance Company at the address above."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<displayWhen>#{CASE.contractLocale=="DC"}</displayWhen>
			</group>
			<group labelWidth="400px"
				style="overflow:auto; height:120px; border:1px solid black">
				<paragragh
					text="I authorize any insurance company, employer, physician, medical professional, hospital, medical facility, pharmacy, pharmacy benefit manager, consumer reporting agency, MIB, Inc. (MIB), or any other person or organization that has any record of information about me to give to Gerber Life Insurance Company, its reinsurers or its authorized representatives, (together, the Company) information about other insurance coverage, employment, age, general character, finances, participation in hazardous activities, medical care or advice about any physical or mental condition, including drug and alcohol treatment information, prescription history records, or other information the Company requires to determine insurability, eligibility for benefits, investigate claims, or support the business operations of the Company related thereto. I authorize Gerber Life Insurance Company or its reinsurers to make a brief report of my personal health information to MIB. I further authorize the sources listed above except MIB to give such information to a consumer reporting agency acting on behalf of Gerber Life Insurance Company. Gerber Life Insurance Company may release information obtained by this Authorization to its reinsurers, to MIB, to other insurers with whom I have policies or to whom I may apply or submit a claim, to other persons or organizations performing business or legal services in connection with an insurance transaction for me, or as may otherwise be lawfully required."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="Any person who knowingly and with intent to injure, defraud or deceive any insurer files a statement of claim or an application containing any false, incomplete or misleading information is guilty of a felony of the third degree."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="I have received a copy of the Notice of Insurance Information Practices. My authorized representative or I may obtain a copy of this Authorization on request. This Authorization will be valid for 24 months from the date signed. It is the Company's practice to prohibit third parties who lawfully receive nonpublic health or other privacy related information from the Company from re-disclosing or reusing the disclosed information. A photographic copy shall be as valid as the original. I understand that a copy of this authorization will be provided, upon request, to me or a person authorized on my behalf. I understand that disclosure of information to the Company may subject the information to re-disclosure in accordance with the Company's privacy policy and MIB rules. Any such re-disclosed information may no longer be protected by federal rules governing privacy and confidentiality. This authorization may be revoked subject to the rights of the Company acting in reliance on the authorization prior to notice of the revocation. Notice of revocation may be sent, in writing, to Gerber Life Insurance Company at the address above."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<displayWhen>#{CASE.contractLocale=="FL" and
					CASE.caseSource=="CAPTIVE"}</displayWhen>
			</group>
			<group labelWidth="400px"
				style="overflow:auto; height:120px; border:1px solid black">
				<paragragh
					text="I authorize any insurance company, employer, physician, medical professional, hospital, medical facility, pharmacy, pharmacy benefit manager, consumer reporting agency, MIB, Inc. (MIB), or any other person or organization that has any record of information about me to give to Gerber Life Insurance Company, its reinsurers or its authorized representatives, (together, the Company) information about other insurance coverage, employment, age, general character, finances, participation in hazardous activities, medical care or advice about any physical or mental condition, including drug and alcohol treatment information, prescription history records, or other information the Company requires to determine insurability, eligibility for benefits, investigate claims, or support the business operations of the Company related thereto. I authorize Gerber Life Insurance Company or its reinsurers to make a brief report of my personal health information to MIB. I further authorize the sources listed above except MIB to give such information to a consumer reporting agency acting on behalf of Gerber Life Insurance Company. Gerber Life Insurance Company may release information obtained by this Authorization to its reinsurers, to MIB, to other insurers with whom I have policies or to whom I may apply or submit a claim, to other persons or organizations performing business or legal services in connection with an insurance transaction for me, or as may otherwise be lawfully required."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="Any person who knowingly and with intent to injure, defraud or deceive any insurer files a statement of claim or an application containing any false, incomplete or misleading information is guilty of a felony of the third degree."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="I have received a copy of the Notice of Insurance Information Practices. My authorized representative or I may obtain a copy of this Authorization on request. This Authorization will be valid for 24 months from the date signed. It is the Company's practice to prohibit third parties who lawfully receive nonpublic health or other privacy related information from the Company from re-disclosing or reusing the disclosed information. A photographic copy shall be as valid as the original. I understand that a copy of this authorization will be provided, upon request, to me or a person authorized on my behalf. I understand that disclosure of information to the Company may subject the information to re-disclosure in accordance with the Company's privacy policy and MIB rules. Any such re-disclosed information may no longer be protected by federal rules governing privacy and confidentiality. This authorization may be revoked subject to the rights of the Company acting in reliance on the authorization prior to notice of the revocation. Notice of revocation may be sent, in writing, to Gerber Life Insurance Company at the address above."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<displayWhen>#{CASE.contractLocale=="FL" and
					CASE.caseSource=="EXTERNAL"}</displayWhen>
			</group>
			<group labelWidth="400px"
				style="overflow:auto; height:120px; border:1px solid black">
				<paragragh
					text="I authorize any insurance company, employer, physician, medical professional, hospital, medical facility, pharmacy, consumer reporting agency, MIB, Inc., or any other person or organization that has any record of information about me to give to Gerber Life Insurance Company, its reinsurers or its authorized representatives, (together, the Company) information about other insurance coverage, employment, age, general character, finances, participation in hazardous activities, medical care or advice about any physical or mental condition, including drug and alcohol treatment information, or other information the Company requires to determine insurability, eligibility for benefits, investigate claims, or support the business operations of the Company related thereto. I authorize Gerber Life Insurance Company or its reinsurer to make a brief report of my personal health information to MIB, Inc. (MIB). I further authorize the sources listed above except MIB, Inc. to give such information to a consumer reporting agency acting on behalf of Gerber Life Insurance Company. Gerber Life Insurance Company may release information obtained by this Authorization to its reinsurers or other insurers with whom I have policies or to whom I may apply or submit a claim, to other persons or organizations performing business or legal services in connection with an insurance transaction for me, or as may otherwise be lawfully required."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="Any person who knowingly presents a false statement in an application for insurance may be guilty of a criminal offense and subject to penalties under state law."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="I have received a copy of the Notice of Insurance Information Practices. I or my authorized representative may obtain a copy of this Authorization on request. This Authorization will be valid for 24 months from the date signed. It is the Company's practice to prohibit third parties who lawfully receive nonpublic health information from re-disclosing or reusing the disclosed information. A photographic copy shall be as valid as the original. I understand that a copy of this authorization will be provided, upon request, to me or a person authorized on my behalf. I understand that disclosure of information to the Company may subject the information to re-disclosure in accordance with the Company's privacy policy and MIB, Inc. rules. This authorization may be revoked; however, it may not be revoked during the contestability period of the policy or to the extent the Company has taken action in reliance on this authorization. Notice of revocation may be sent, in writing, to Gerber Life Insurance Company at the address above."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<displayWhen>#{CASE.contractLocale=="SD"}</displayWhen>
			</group>
			<group labelWidth="400px"
				style="overflow:auto; height:120px; border:1px solid black">
				<paragragh
					text="I authorize any insurance company, employer, physician, medical professional, hospital, medical facility, pharmacy, pharmacy benefit manager, consumer reporting agency, MIB, Inc. (MIB), or any other person or organization that has any record of information about me to give to Gerber Life Insurance Company, its reinsurers or its authorized representatives, (together, the Company) information about other insurance coverage, employment, age, general character, finances, participation in hazardous activities, medical care or advice about any physical or mental condition, including drug and alcohol treatment information, prescription history records, or other information the Company requires to determine insurability, eligibility for benefits, investigate claims, or support the business operations of the Company related thereto. I authorize Gerber Life Insurance Company or its reinsurers to make a brief report of my personal health information to MIB. I further authorize the sources listed above except MIB to give such information to a consumer reporting agency acting on behalf of Gerber Life Insurance Company. Gerber Life Insurance Company may release information obtained by this Authorization to its reinsurers, to MIB, to other insurers with whom I have policies or to whom I may apply or submit a claim, to other persons or organizations performing business or legal services in connection with an insurance transaction for me, or as may otherwise be lawfully required."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="I have received a copy of the Notice of Insurance Information Practices. My authorized representative or I may obtain a copy of this Authorization on request. This Authorization will be valid for 24 months from the date signed. It is the Company's practice to prohibit third parties who lawfully receive nonpublic health or other privacy related information from the Company from re-disclosing or reusing the disclosed information. A photographic copy shall be as valid as the original. I understand that a copy of this authorization will be provided, upon request, to me or a person authorized on my behalf. I understand that disclosure of information to the Company may subject the information to re-disclosure in accordance with the Company's privacy policy and MIB rules. Any such re-disclosed information will be subject to the protections of Montana law section 33-19-306, but may no longer be protected by federal rules governing privacy and confidentiality. This authorization may be revoked; however, it may not be revoked during the contestability period of the policy or to the extent the Company has taken action in reliance on this authorization. Notice of revocation may be sent, in writing, to Gerber Life Insurance Company at the address above."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="I have received a copy of the Notice of Insurance Information Practices. I or my authorized representative may obtain a copy of this Authorization on request. This Authorization will be valid for 24 months from the date signed. It is the Company's practice to prohibit third parties who lawfully receive nonpublic health information from re-disclosing or reusing the disclosed information. A photographic copy shall be as valid as the original. I understand that a copy of this authorization will be provided, upon request, to me or a person authorized on my behalf. I understand that disclosure of information to the Company may subject the information to re-disclosure in accordance with the Company's privacy policy and MIB, Inc. rules. This authorization may be revoked; however, it may not be revoked during the contestability period of the policy or to the extent the Company has taken action in reliance on this authorization. Notice of revocation may be sent, in writing, to Gerber Life Insurance Company at the address above."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<displayWhen>#{CASE.contractLocale=="MT"}</displayWhen>
			</group>
			<group labelWidth="400px"
				style="overflow:auto; height:120px; border:1px solid black">
				<paragragh
					text="I authorize any insurance company, employer, physician, medical professional, hospital, medical facility, pharmacy, pharmacy benefit manager, consumer reporting agency, MIB, Inc. (MIB), or any other person or organization that has any record of information about me to give to Gerber Life Insurance Company, its reinsurers or its authorized representatives, (together, the Company) information about other insurance coverage, employment, age, general character, finances, participation in hazardous activities, medical care or advice about any physical or mental condition, prescription history records, or other information the Company requires to determine insurability, eligibility for benefits, investigate claims, or support the business operations of the Company related thereto. I authorize Gerber Life Insurance Company or its reinsurers to make a brief report of my personal health information to MIB. I further authorize the sources listed above except MIB to give such information to a consumer reporting agency acting on behalf of Gerber Life Insurance Company. I authorize Gerber Life Insurance Company to cause to be prepared an investigative consumer report in connection with this application. Gerber Life Insurance Company may release information obtained by this Authorization to its reinsurers, to MIB, to other insurers with whom I have policies or to whom I may apply or submit a claim, to other persons or organizations performing business or legal services in connection with an insurance transaction for me, or as may otherwise be lawfully required."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="I have received a copy of the Notice of Insurance Information Practices. My authorized representative or I may obtain a copy of this Authorization on request. This Authorization will be valid for 24 months from the date signed. It is the Company's practice to prohibit third parties who lawfully receive nonpublic health or other privacy related information from the Company from re-disclosing or reusing the disclosed information. A photographic copy shall be as valid as the original. I understand that a copy of this authorization will be provided, upon request, to me or a person authorized on my behalf. I understand that disclosure of information to the Company may subject the information to re-disclosure in accordance with the Company's privacy policy and MIB rules. Any such re-disclosed information may no longer be protected by federal rules governing privacy and confidentiality. This authorization may be revoked. Notice of revocation may be sent, in writing, to Gerber Life Insurance Company at the address above."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<displayWhen>#{CASE.contractLocale=="NY"}</displayWhen>
			</group>
			<group labelWidth="400px" title="Full HIPAA"
				style="overflow:auto; height:250px; border:1px solid black">
				<paragragh text="PURPOSES" styleClass="groupParagraphBold"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="This authorization applies to any Personal Information (defined below) that may be obtained, used, or disclosed about the Proposed Insured by the Gerber Life Insurance Company (the &quot;Company,&quot; &quot;we&quot;, or &quot;us&quot;) for the purpose of determining the Proposed Insured&apos;s eligibility for insurance, which may include the processing of an application for insurance or any other legally permissible activities that relate to any coverage with the Company."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh text="PERSONAL INFORMATION" styleClass="groupParagraphBold"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="I understand and agree that the types of &quot;Personal Information&quot; that may be obtained, used, or disclosed about the Proposed Insured on the basis of this authorization may include, to the extent permitted by law: "
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="(i) any and all health records about the Proposed Insured, including, but not limited to, information regarding medical, mental, or physical condition and treatment, prescription drug history, lab results, drug or alcohol use, and the diagnosis and treatment of Human Immunodeficiency Virus (&quot;HIV&quot;) or other sexually transmitted diseases; and, "
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="(ii) non-health information about the Proposed Insured, including, but not limited to, information regarding finances, demographics (date of birth, birthplace, state of residence, etc.), employment, general reputation, insurance (including previous application activities), credit history, criminal history, and driving history. "
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>

				<paragragh
					text="Personal Information does not include psychotherapy notes unless such notes are included with the medical record. "
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh text="AUTHORIZATION FOR OTHERS TO DISCLOSE TO US"
					styleClass="groupParagraphBold"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="I authorize all of the following classes of people or entities to disclose Personal Information about the Proposed Insured to the Company and its authorized agents and representatives: physicians, medical practitioners, hospitals, clinics, laboratories, pharmacies, pharmacy benefit managers, medical care facilities, and all other providers of medical services or sources of medical records; consumer reporting agencies; financial sources; business associates; past or current employers; benefit plan sponsors; government units, including the Department of Motor Vehicles; the Medical Information Bureau (MIB); and insurance companies. I further authorize the Company, and its authorized agents and representatives, to collect and process such Personal Information. By signing below, I acknowledge that any prior agreement I have made to restrict or limit the disclosure of Personal Information about the Proposed Insured does not apply to this authorization."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="AUTHORIZATION FOR US TO DISCLOSE TO OTHERS (AND POTENTIAL FOR RE-DISCLOSURE)"
					styleClass="groupParagraphBold"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="I understand that the Company may disclose Personal Information for the purposes stated in this authorization to the Company's underwriters, administrators, reinsurers, contractors or others who may perform business services for the Company, or to the beneficiaries or other owners of the Proposed Insured's policy. In addition, Personal Information may be disclosed (i) to the Medical Information Bureau (MIB) in an effort to deter fraud, misrepresentation, or criminal activity, or (ii) as otherwise required or permitted by law. Personal Information which is used or disclosed pursuant to this authorization may be subject to re-disclosure by the recipient, and may no longer be protected under federal or state privacy laws. "
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh text="FAILURE TO SIGN" styleClass="groupParagraphBold"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="I understand that I may refuse to sign this authorization. I realize that if I refuse to sign, the Company may not be able to issue the insurance for which I am applying or may not be able to make benefit payments."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh text="DURATION AND REVOCATION" styleClass="groupParagraphBold"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="Unless revoked earlier, this authorization will remain in effect for 24 months* from the date signed. I understand that I may revoke this authorization at any time, by written notice to: "
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh text="Gerber Life Insurance Company"
					styleClass="groupParagraphCenter"></paragragh>
				<paragragh text="ATTN: Underwriting Department"
					styleClass="groupParagraphCenter"></paragragh>
				<paragragh text="445 State Street" styleClass="groupParagraphCenter"></paragragh>
				<paragragh text="Fremont, MI 49412" styleClass="groupParagraphCenter"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="I understand that my right to revoke this authorization is limited to the extent that the Company has already taken action in reliance upon this authorization or the law allows the Company to contest the issuance of a policy or a claim under a policy. "
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh text="COPIES OF THIS FORM" styleClass="groupParagraphBold"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="I agree that a copy of this authorization form (including faxes and electronic transmissions of this form) will be as valid as the original for purposes of obtaining or disclosing the required Personal Information about the Proposed Insured. I also understand that I am entitled to obtain a copy of this authorization form."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<displayWhen>#{securityController.userIdentity.securityUser.partyType=='PRIMARY_INSURED'}</displayWhen>
			</group>
			<group labelWidth="400px" title="Notices"
				style="overflow:auto; height:120px; border:1px solid black">
				<paragragh text="FCRA NOTICE" styleClass="groupParagraphBold"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="Depending on the size of the policy applied for, we may request that an investigative consumer report about the Proposed Insured be given to us.  It will be conducted by a national organization skilled in obtaining information about people.  A credit report may be requested in connection with this application to determine eligibility of insurance or premium to be charged. The kind of information we may be seeking includes such facts as residence verification, marital status, occupation, general reputation, personal characteristics and mode of living.  It will be obtained through personal interviews with the Proposed Insured&apos;s friends, neighbors, associates and other acquaintances.  Inquiries will not be directed toward determining the Proposed Insured&apos;s sexual orientation."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="The Proposed Insured, upon written request will be informed whether or not an investigative report was requested, and if a report was ordered, the name and address of the Consumer reporting agency.  A copy of this report is available to the Proposed Insured upon request."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh text="MIB NOTICE" styleClass="groupParagraphBold"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="Information regarding your insurability will be treated as confidential. Gerber Life Insurance Company or its reinsurers may, however, make a brief report thereon to the MIB, Inc., formerly known as Medical Information Bureau, a not-for-profit membership organization of insurance companies, which operates an information exchange on behalf of its members. If you apply to another MIB member company for life or health insurance coverage, or a claim for benefits is submitted to such a company, MIB, upon request, will supply such company with the information about you in its file."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="Upon receipt of a request from you, MIB will arrange disclosure of any information in your file. Please contact MIB at 866-692-6901 (TTY 866-346-3642). If you question the accuracy of the information in MIB&apos;s file, you may contact MIB and seek a correction in accordance with the procedures set forth in the federal Fair Credit Reporting Act. The address of MIB&apos;s information office is (50 Braintree Hill Park, Suite 400, Braintree, Massachusetts 02184-8734)."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="Gerber Life Insurance Company, or its reinsurers, may also release information from its file to other insurance companies to whom you may apply for life or health insurance, or to whom a claim for benefits may be submitted. Information for consumers about MIB may be obtained on its website at www.mib.com."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
			</group>
			<group labelWidth="400px" title=" "
				style="overflow:auto; height:100px; border:1px solid black">
				<paragragh text="Notice of Information Practices"
					styleClass="groupParagraphBold"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="To approve your insurance and service your policy, we may collect or disclose information about you, as permitted by law, which may include certain disclosures made without your prior authorization.  You have the right to access and correct personal information that we have about you.  You may also receive a detailed notice on Gerber Life&apos;s Information Practices, upon request."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<displayWhen>#{CASE.contractLocale == 'CT' or CASE.contractLocale ==
					'VA' or CASE.contractLocale == 'OR' or CASE.contractLocale == 'OH'
					or CASE.contractLocale == 'NC' or CASE.contractLocale == 'NJ' or
					CASE.contractLocale == 'NV' or CASE.contractLocale == 'MT' or
					CASE.contractLocale == 'MN' or CASE.contractLocale == 'MA' or
					CASE.contractLocale == 'ME' or CASE.contractLocale == 'IL' or
					CASE.contractLocale == 'GA' or CASE.contractLocale == 'CN' or
					CASE.contractLocale == 'CA' or CASE.contractLocale == 'AZ'}
				</displayWhen>
			</group>
			<group labelWidth="400px" title=" "
				style="overflow:auto; height:100px; border:1px solid black">
				<paragragh text="Important Replacement Notice" styleClass="groupParagraphBold"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="It may not be in your best interest to replace an existing life insurance policy or annuity contract when purchasing a new life insurance policy, whether from the same of a different insurer.  A replacement will occur if, as part of your purchase of a new life insurance policy, existing coverage has been, or is likely to be, lapsed, surrendered, forfeited, assigned, terminated, changed or modified into paid-up insurance or other forms of benefits, loaned against or withdrawn from, reduced in value by use of cash values or other policy values, changed in the length of time or in the amount of insurance that would continue, or continued with a stoppage or reduction in the amount of premium paid. Prior to replacing an insurance coverage, you may want to contact the insurance company or agent who sold you that coverage, to help you decide whether the replacement is in your best interest."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<displayWhen>#{CASE.contractLocale == 'NY'}</displayWhen>
			</group>
			<group labelWidth="400px" title="PART 4"
				style="overflow:auto; height:120px; border:1px solid black">
				<paragragh
					text="It is understood and agreed that:"
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="All statements and answers made in all parts of this application are true and complete to the best of my knowledge and belief, and shall be the basis for and become part of any policy issued as a result of this application. Other than as stated in any conditional receipt, any policy issued will not take effect until it has been approved and the initial full premium(s) due have been received by the Company while the proposed insured is alive and all statements and answers in all parts of the application continue to be true and complete. I will notify the Company of any changes to the statements and answers given in any part of the application which occur before the policy is approved and payment is received by the Company."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<displayWhen>#{CASE.contractLocale!="CT" and CASE.contractLocale!="NY"}</displayWhen>
			</group>
			<group labelWidth="400px" title="PART 4"
				style="overflow:auto; height:120px; border:1px solid black">
				<paragragh
					text="It is understood and agreed that:"
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="All statements and answers made in all parts of this application are true and complete to the best of my knowledge and belief, and shall be the basis for and become part of any policy issued as a result of this application. Other than as stated in any conditional receipt, any policy issued will not take effect until it has been approved and the initial full premium(s) due have been received by the Company while the proposed insured is alive and all statements and answers in all parts of the application continue to be true and complete. I will notify the Company of any changes to the statements and answers given in any part of the application which occur before the policy is approved and payment is received by the Company. Review the answers on this application carefully. If any of your answers are incorrect or untrue, even if unintentional, the Company has the right to deny benefits or rescind your coverage."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<displayWhen>#{CASE.contractLocale=="CT"}</displayWhen>
			</group>
			<group labelWidth="400px" title="PART 4"
				style="overflow:auto; height:120px; border:1px solid black">
				<paragragh
					text="It is understood and agreed that:"
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<paragragh
					text="All statements and answers made in all parts of this application are true and complete to the best of my knowledge and belief. This application will be attached to the policy. Any policy issued will not take effect until it has been approved and the initial full premium(s) due have been received by the Company while the proposed insured is alive. I will notify the Company of any changes to the statements and answers given in any part of the application which occur before the policy is approved and payment is received by the Company."
					styleClass="groupParagraph"></paragragh>
				<displayWhen>#{CASE.contractLocale=="NY"}</displayWhen>
			</group>
		</section>
		
	</page>
</form>